workoninternet.com 2015-12-04

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is of the utmost importance to the WorkOnInternet.com Online Community. Because we ask for some basic personal information during registration, we want you to be fully informed of how this information is gathered and used.

  1. [REGISTRATION](http://site.workoninternet.com/business/privacy-policy.html#registration)
  2. [INFORMATION THE WORKONINTERNET.COM COMMUNITY REQUESTS](http://site.workoninternet.com/business/privacy-policy.html#info)
  3. [CHILDREN'S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT](http://site.workoninternet.com/business/privacy-policy.html#coppa)
  4. [PARTICIPATION](http://site.workoninternet.com/business/privacy-policy.html#participation)
  5. [COOKIES](http://site.workoninternet.com/business/privacy-policy.html#cookies)
  6. [WORKONINTERNET.COM FORUM](http://site.workoninternet.com/business/privacy-policy.html#workoninternet)
  7. [COOKIES](http://site.workoninternet.com/business/privacy-policy.html#cookies)
  8. [ADVERTISING](http://site.workoninternet.com/business/privacy-policy.html#ads)
  9. [PUBLIC AREA](http://site.workoninternet.com/business/privacy-policy.html#public)
  10. [SECURITY](http://site.workoninternet.com/business/privacy-policy.html#security)
  11. [FUTURN CHANGE](http://site.workoninternet.com/business/privacy-policy.html#future)
  12. [](http://site.workoninternet.com/business/privacy-policy.html#summary)[SUMMARY](http://site.workoninternet.com/business/privacy-policy.html#summary)

---  
  
Some basic personal information is required in order to register with the WorkOnInternet.com community:

  *  **Name** \- Your first and last name help us to personalize your online experience. 
  *  **Email Address** \- By providing your email address, you can receive important messages via your existing email account. Message board notifications, personalized My newsletters, and messages sent to you by other members rely on the email address you provide when you register. 
  * **User Name** \- This is how you are identified when you participate in the community. While many other aspects of your account can be updated regularly, your user name cannot be changed.

After you register, you are encouraged to give demographic information (like birth year, occupation, and gender). We ask you to tell us a little about yourself so we can better understand the types of people who register. This information can also be used to provide you with content that may be of interest to you, and to show you advertisements that are relevant to your demographic information. The website uses outside ad companies to display ads on its sites. These ads may contain cookies. While the site uses cookies in other parts of its sites, the ad companies also use cookies with the ads displayed, and we may not have access to this information.

No children under 13 are allowed to participate in WorkOnInternet.com community, including the community's forum.

The above describes information that is provided "actively" - meaning, you choose to submit this information to us when you join WorkOnInternet.com community, or update your account/profile at any point after having joined. Some other information is provided "passively" - meaning, that WorkOnInternet.com community obtains this information when you login to your account and use the service. This is done primarily through the use of "cookies." Cookies are used on WorkOnInternet.com to verify your login information, and to optionally store your password in your browser so that you do not need to type it in each time you visit. Any time that you point your browser to a 'members-only' area, The community checks your browser's cookie file to see if you have already logged in, and if you have, you're taken right to the page that you have requested. If not, you'll be directed to the login screen, where you can quickly and easily login to your account, or signup for the community if you are not yet a member. Cookies are also used in conjunction with some ad banners to determine their effectiveness.

WorkOnInternet.com community uses cookies to customize your experience while using our services. A cookie is a small text file that many Web sites write through your browser when you visit them. A cookie can only be read by the site that places it, so the community can't learn about your browsing history based on any other cookies in your browser. Most browsers also allow the option of displaying a warning before accepting a cookie, or refusing all cookies. Declining cookies while participating in the community may result in some of features not working properly.

The community uses third-party advertising companies and advertising networks to serve ads to you on our behalf when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Personally identifiable information such as your name, address, email address or telephone number are not shared with advertisers without your permission. We may use personally identifiable information in order to fill in forms on third-party sites we use to present advertising offers. But this information will not be shared and will not be stored by any third parties if you decline these offers.

The third-party advertising company that we currently uses is Google. For more information on their privacy policies, please consult the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

As a registered user, you may receive informational email messages from WorkOnInternet.com community from time to time. All registered members are required to receive such communications. If you wish to stop these emails, you may This e-mail address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it at any time.

The website hosts a board, an online community with a gallery library and other services for both public and private purpose. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in public becomes public information. In addition, information that is disclosed in private places may be disclosed by other public services of the website. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

The website has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under its control. WorkOnInternet.com       servers have strict security in place to prevent an intruder from retrieving personal information about its users. We are the sole owner of any information that you post within the website.

From time to time, we may use user information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

In this electronic era, when personal information can easily be obtained through various sources, We appreciates the sensitivity of any private information that you disclose to us. It is our intention to treat your account information with the highest level of care.
